Yay! Catching up to #1!
Yes, vinyl is good too.
We need you to keep up the good work!
Pretty for you, not at least a chain of events
I want to make it happen with you
On my damn mind
Tell me now It doesn't mean anything
If it's words, I don't need them anymore
It's up now, it's up now
You and me so ume ni
Now the next one plays backwards!
I still don't get it.
You really don't understand reverse playback, do you?
I don't think so.
Let's go. Question 13: Rainfall Superintro 9
Oh, that was easy.
Michie.
I can't get you to talk.
You're acting like you're not interested
Hey Hey Hey
It's called "Hey Hey Hey".
I think this is the most popular song
I think it's the most popular song among the audience.
Together with the song
The chorus is really catchy.
The choruses are so catchy, like "sodsukae furifuri" and "nekochan".
and "batten down the hatches" and "right, left, right, left".
I think it's a song you can enjoy while dancing with the audience.
I hope you can enjoy dancing to this song at the concert.
Sayaka's eyes are starting to light up a little.
I can finally see hope.
I'll allow only you to put it here.
May I?
I'm right here.
Got it!
Question 14: Rainfall Superintro 9
Oh, I get it.
I don't know.
I get it.
Artificial bar?
I have no idea.
Halothon.
Lucky number.
Yay.
My head.
I don't want to feel
You two so lucky so lucky
my no.1
Yes, this song is...
It's a very cute song.
You can say "lucky, lucky, lucky" in the choreography.
You can enjoy this song with this song.
It's a very cute song by AmeFlash.
It's cute, but it's a stylish song.
And we're all friends.
Yes, yes, yes.
So I think people of all ages can get into it.
Please give it a listen!
Question 15: Ameflash Super Intro 9
You got this one, didn't you?
Here's the question.
I'll give it to you, Moyaka.
Oh, my God, it's a present!
A present.
Wow.
I get it.
You know what I mean.
What was that?
You're kidding.
I don't know.
Listen to this.
Then I'll give you a hint.
I've heard a lot of idols singing.
At the moment.
They do it outside of live shows, too, don't they?
Even outside of live performances.
I've been using them a lot lately.
Do you want to hear it again? Based on that...
Did you get it?
It's not like I understand what you're saying.
It's like you already know what I'm talking about.
Flapjack morning.
What took you so long?
I'm not sure I'm cut out for this.
I'm sorry.
It's no problem.
I don't know what to do.
Flap, flap, flap, flap, flap!
Hurriyah hurriyah!
is
These lyrics are about getting ready in the morning
It's a song about a girl getting ready in the morning.
Makeup before a concert
Listen to it when you leave the house
or before you leave the house.
It's a perfect song for you, so please listen to it.
Oh my God, what am I going to do?
I really don't know what to do.It's just like I was writing tips, really.
Really good.
Try to put in so many!
The next one is a four song mix!
Wow.
Is this the final one?
Yes, sir.
Oh, my God.
You have to answer all of them.
Yes.
Oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God.
But... four songs... that's too many.
It's a mess.
Is that a point?
I don't know.
Two points for this one.
I'm going to get it right.
We can all catch up now.
Let's go for it.
Amefurashi Super Intro 9
I got two right... two right...
I don't know four.
I wish they'd play this on every spur of the moment.
Can't we do it again?
I know 2 songs for sure.
Drama and Tantooinster.
Right?
The Rainmakers.
I don't know.
How many are these?
Only two.
Two songs?
Two songs. That's right.
Oh, my God.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
It's too loud.
It's a little insistent.
Can you turn off the drama?
Then I'll answer for sure.
Can you play something else?
I'm sorry, please.
Okay, okay, okay, I understand.
Shut up.
What?
Artificial Girl and...
Drama and tantrums and tantrums and tantrums.
Assatta's the better kind.
Oh!
There's a very small one.
I'll sing four songs.
No, thank you.
That's what I'm talking about.
Sing a mix of songs.
I can't.
Sing four songs.
Please sing four songs.
Sing four songs, please.
Please sing four songs
Please sing four songs.
Please sing 4 songs
Please sing a mix of songs
I can't.
Just a mix.
Can you give it a shot?
You can do it.
So many artifacts.
There really are.
I didn't hear the most.
You were the most assertive.
I didn't hear the artificial girl.
I didn't hear the other way around.
I'm still not sure.
The rain drop is falling presents
It's like...
It's the image of Disney or the beginning of a parade or something.
It's a song with a lot of showcases.
I'm sure you'll enjoy dancing to it at the live performance.
I think it will be a song that you can enjoy dancing to.
Are the chopsticks better for Asatta?
When we were the first 5 members...
It's a song that has been around since our early days.
Psyllium is a song that creates a sense of togetherness.
It's a song that creates a sense of togetherness.
And also
Tantwister is a song
There are some fast words in it.
There are catchy choreographies that everyone can dance together.
There are catchy choreographies that everyone can dance together
I'd like you to dance together with them.
One more thing
Drama
You know, that TikTok thing.
Chuch Chuch Chuch Chuch
It's very popular.
It's a reference to the choreography.
Some of the choreography is really catchy.
And you can enjoy the sound.And I enjoy the sound.
It's a very enjoyable song.
Please listen to it if you like.
It's a very good song, isn't it?
I've been listening to it a lot.
Yes!
Ameracis Super Interrookid!
Steering?
How many of these did I get right?
What? Are you kidding me?
You're sure?
Because Blue and Rain definitely match, right?
Maybe Rain is missing.
What?
One more time, please!
Wow!
Yes!
Okay, four songs, please!
Blue, Love is Love.
Oh, okay,
What was that?
Are you kidding me?
Europe?
Net-a-mole foos!
Where's Netamor Fords?
There was a Netamor Fords.
It's in the first place, isn't it?
Oh, there he is!
Netamor Fords.
It's the song that gets everyone jumping.
It's a great song.
We all jumped together.
There's a great sense of togetherness.
It's a very fun song.
And Love is Love
L-O-V-E
It's a song with a lot of L-O-V-E moves in it
that we didn't even know existed.
that we didn't even know were in there.
I thought it would be fun for people to see the choreography and think, "Oh, there's L-O-V-E in it.
It's a cool song that we hope people will enjoy.
It's a cool song!
Blue" is a song that really
It's a song for female adults.
There is a music video for this song.
If you watch the music video
If you see the music video, I think you will like the atmosphere of this song.
Dark Face!
Dark Face is a song about
A woman who looks bad.
I think her expression is the highlight of the song.
I think the highlight of the song is her facial expressions.
It's a rare song if you can see it.
If you can see it, it's a rare song.
It's the rarest song in the world.
She doesn't seem to grow up or anything.
He's the most tired.
I'm so tired.
So, there's only one question left.
Shall we make it one yen?
Hana-chan...
Six for Aiara.
I'll take four.
I'll take 5.
So that means it's a good close game
That means
If I get three points next time, I win?
For both of you.
But we'll take two points.
We'll be fine.
The last problem is...
Bonus points are usually...
I'll just ask for a favor from Aiara and Yuzu.
I'm counting on you.
Sorry.
Final problem Amehara Murasaki Super Intro 9
Music
Ten more steps to go
Enough Rainmakers Under the Rain In the Madding Crowd
Yeah!
Huh!
Where is it? Where is it?
I don't know! I don't hear any of that!
Is this okay?
Yes!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Anders Lane is our...
I beg your pardon.
No Under's Lane.
He said something about mainmakers.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Anders Lane is no good.
Under's Lane is our strong...
Not me!
You shouldn't do this.
It's not me, but the staff.
Sh!
What? Why the staff?
It's Suzuki who feels he has to do it at a time like that.
It's a song with a strong will,It is a song with a strong will,
We often play this song at the end of our live performances,
We often play this song at the end of our live performances, and I think it fits our strong feelings,
We often play this song at the end of our live performances, and I think our strong feelings are in this song, so I hope we can convey our will to you,
This song is 100 seconds long,
This song is a little bit unique and unusual,
It's a little bit unique song, but it's a little bit strange. Tant-tat-tat-tat, key!
In the middle of the song, there is a part where the song goes "tan-tat-tan, ha!
I think it's great because everyone dances to it and gets excited.
What else?
Rainmakers is a song from our early days,
The chorus is like shaking your shoulders,
It is a song that represents Ameflasi in this process of growth,
It is one of the representative songs of Amefurashi in this process of growth,
I would like to make everyone shake their shoulders together in a cheerful way.
The last one is in Zato,
We don't often perform this song live,
It is a ballad song that conveys emotions with the body,
It is a ballad song that conveys emotions with the body, so that everyone can see the beautiful and beautiful expression of the song while keeping it quiet.
Natto is different, too!
It's long! I think.
We have to convey the song properly!
The winner was Yumi Ichikawa, who won by cheating by dividing the music into notes without guessing,
Yumi Ichikawa! Congratulations!
She won!
I didn't cheat or anything.
No way!
Did you do this to her?
Sorry!
So, I was the first intro princess, Yumi Ichikawa!
You might need an intro dance.